bizwaremagic.com 2011-03-13

# Privacy Policy

|  |     **Privacy Policy**

    Preamble
    
    BizwareMagic.com understands that you may have concerns about safeguarding
    your privacy on-line. The Privacy Statement that follows explains our views and
    practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as you make full
    use of our many offerings. This statement discloses the privacy practices for all
    of our websites including the website you are currently visiting where you are
    reading this Privacy Policy.

    BizwareMagic.com, respects the privacy of all its users. The privacy policies 
    below are in effect for the BizwareMagic website and newsletters or ezines. 
    
    No Spam
    
    BizwareMagic does not tolerate or practice any form of spam. We do not give 
    your email address or contact information to any third-party organizations. 
    There is an 'unsubscribe' link or form on each email that is sent. Subscribers 
    may Opt-Out at any time. We follow the "CAN-SPAM Act".
    
    Data Collection
    
    BizwareMagic only collects information (first name, email and IP address/signup 
    time) for its newsletters and is not used for any other purposes. Removal from 
    these newsletters can be done from the removal links placed in each and all emails.
    
    We don't knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 
    If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, it
    will be deleted from our systems. This site is of little interest to children and
    this issue should not be a problem. However, if any parent or guardian has any concerns 
    they may contact this site to get any such details removed immediately.
    contact (at) bizwaremagic.com
    
    Cookies
    BizwareMagic does not use any cookies to track customer habits or behavior.
    The only exception is that Google Adsense does use the DoubleClick DART cookie:
    
    We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. 
    These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, 
    or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide 
    advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more 
    information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information 
    used by these companies, go here: http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx

    Opt-In
    Any and all newsletters associated with and operated by BizwareMagic.com are 
    totally double OPT-IN. Visitors must opt-in or give permission for follow-up 
    emails. They must opt-in twice to receive information from this site. This 
    prevents anyone from simply signing up with false or someone else's contact details.
    Subscribers can opt-out at any time by using the removal links in all emails.

    Opt-Out
    If, at any time, you wish to be removed from the BizwareMagic Newsletters, 
    you can use the removal link that's placed in every email.

    Contacting This Website
    
    If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this
    site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:
    
    contact (at) bizwaremagic.com

[](http://www.bizwaremagic.com/site-map.htm) Please feel free to contact us.  

**© Copyright - 2006-2020 All Rights Reserved.** [Earnings Disclaimer](http://www.bizwaremagic.com/Disclaimer.htm) |   
---|---|---
